yuuby.com 2015-04-07

# Yuuby | Privacy Policy

Controlling Your Information

We respect the privacy of our members. We want to make Yuuby a place for exchange and sharing where you can easily manage your personnal information. We agree to abide with the following:

Easily Manage your Privacy

Introduction

Our Privacy Policy covers all aspects of the processing of your personal information by Yuuby. However, it does not apply to external sites that Yuuby does not have or control, this include existing applications. When you use Yuuby, you agree to our Privacy Policy described below by the following:

Policy About Minors

Minors under 13 are not allowed to register on Yuuby or give us information about them. Yuuby will delete as soon as possible any relevant information. You can participate in that commitment by notifying us of all minors under 13 by following the link [Report Fake Profile](http://www.yuuby.com/report_fake_profile).

We recommends that minors 13 years of age or older ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet. We encourage parents to teach their children about safe internet use practices.

Protecting Your Information

We use sophisticated technology to secure your information. Here's how we do:

**Connection.** Whenever you connect to Yuuby, we use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) to encrypt your information. This way, you are protected any attempt to access your account. We recommend choosing a password "strong" (a combination of uppercase and lowercase letters, numbers and symbols) and using antivirus software.

**Personal Information.** When you manage your [Account Settings](http://www.yuuby.com/privacy) we use the SSL technology to secure your information. Only you can manage your settings or update your information.

**Payments.** We secure your payments in two ways, when you submit your payment information (SSL), then when we communicate such information to your payment source issuer (platform secure bank) required to process this transaction. So you submit your transaction information encrypted as we pass safely again.

**Report an Offense.** You can help us make Yuuby safer. For that, you don't hesitate to notify us of any links or violation of our Terms of Use. Use the following links: [Report Fake Profile.](http://www.yuuby.com/report_fake_profile) or [IP Infringement](http://www.yuuby.com/copyright_notice).

**Risks in Sharing.** We give you ways to allow people you want to access your information. However, we cannot control how users will use our personal information. Depending on the privacy settings you've established, your information may have been copied by other users. So, we cannot guarantee that only users whom you have granted access will see your information.

Collected Information

**Sign Up Process.** When you sign up for Yuuby, we ask for your name, email address, date of birth and sex. If you wish, you may also state your political and religious views. Of course, your privacy settings allow you to manage who can access this information.

**Friend Finder.** Once your sign up process is completed, you will be able to find friends already on Yuuby, or using our Friend Finder.

**Share with Friends.** From your Yuuby account, you can share more with friends by adding personal information (profile picture, academic networks, hometown and current, relationships and interests). You may also share other content, such as status, links, albums and music you like. You can delete or change any information at your leisure.

**Friends of Friends.** Your friends may list a relationship with you. You may also have been tagged on a photo or video by a user not one your friend list. However, you can delete these tags and refuse any friend requests or relationships.

**Adding Friend, Page... .** When you visit a profile of a friend, group, page, event, application, or share any contents, we saved this information to provide you relevant contents.

**Ways to Access.** When you log in to Yuuby, we collect information about your ways of access, such as, your access device (computer, mobile phone or other device) and the type of browser you use. To provide you our experience, we also collect other information about the pages you visit, your current location and your IP address.

**About Cookies.** We use "cookies" (small data file transferred to the computer hard drive) to make Yuuby easier to use. We may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how users interact with our services. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies. However, you can remove or block cookies using the settings in your browser.

Privacy On Yuuby

Through your [Privacy Settings](http://www.yuuby.com/privacy), you may restrain access to your information. We recommend that you set this page as soon as possible.

**Privacy Settings.** You may restrict your contents through these ways:

  * **Everyone.** Any information set to "Everyone" is available for every Yuuby users, and may be used, distributed, imported, exported, and redistributed by us and others without privacy limitations. However, your information is not indexed by other search engines. This parameter can be easily changed from the [Privacy Settings](http://www.yuuby.com/privacy).

We cannot control this information outside Yuuby.

We don't share any Personal Information about you to a third part.

  * **Friends and Networks** When you apply this privacy setting to a post, you only allow Friends and Networks to access this information.

  * **Friends of Friends** Through this privacy setting, you authorized access to Friends and Users (e.g., friends and users whom your friends are linked.)

**General Information.** General Information are not "confidential" data, they guarantee the identity of Yuuby users. Included are, your name, first name, networks and interests, this information can be indexed by third party search engines. You can set your visibility outside Yuuby through your Privacy Settings.

**Information you manage.** Besides General Information, you can manage any other information. You may define the access to your information. For example, you may define how other users access your Contact Information, Date of birth or your post (status, photos, videos and links).

**You and Friends.** When you share a post (such as your status, photo, event...), your friends may view this post through their [Home page](http://www.yuuby.com/home).

Some of your information may be viewed on other pages. This information may be shared again by other users.

The information you post on profiles of other users will be governed by the privacy settings of the user's account.

**Links.** When you click a link, you can leave Yuuby. In this case, we cannot guarantee the security of this third party website, remember to check if it is safe. Yuuby prohibits any links that hurt a person or group of people, you can report this link by going to the page concerned.

**Advertising.** Some advertises in Yuuby may use cookies to evaluate the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. However, you may also use your browser cookie settings to limit or prevent the placement of cookies by advertising networks.

Yuuby and You

You can use your privacy settings to manage how your information may be shared. We may use different ways to improve your experience on Yuuby. For example:

**To give you news.** We may directly communicate with you on your profile or send you messages in your Yuuby Inbox. This is necessary to keep you informed about any Yuuby updates or new features.

**Your profile is updating.** We may use some information provided by other users to complete your profile. For example, when you are tagged in a photo or video, this information will be posted on your profile. This feature allows you to control your identity on Yuuby.

**Security.** To ensure the safety, we prevent abuse such as click fraud or suspicious text. If you are repeatedly report, we will disable your account when appropriate.

**Suggestions.** We help you to find friends. For this, we suggest other users using profile's information (such as contacts list, invitation or personal friends of friends). Similarly, we suggest your profile if your email included in a contact list or if you are related to one of these friends. You can restrict your visibility on Yuuby through your Privacy Settings.

**Customized advertising.** To optimize your Yuuby experience, we just present to you ads you may like. However, we don't use any personal information such as your name or first name.

**Advertise between you and friends.** When you link a page to your profile (for example the page of your favorite artist), we may associate your name and photo to ads content that is edited by the owner of this page. Only friends will be able to view it. For example, when you linked the page of your favorite artists to your profile, we link your name and photo if the ad content published by your favorite artist page is viewed by your friends. Expect your friends, this link between you and your page will not be visible to any user.

**Sponsored posts.** When you vote for sponsored posts, your choice is saved but no personal information is disclosed. We use your choice to offer you custom advertising contents. For example, if you decide to participate in a sponsored event, we consider only your choice. Your name and photo are not provided.

Sharing

Yuuby is the social sharing place to discuss media contents with your friends. You may share media contents with everyone, we provide ways to set our profile to allow who you want to share your information on your profile through your [Privacy Settings](http://www.yuuby.com/privacy). In order to guarantee our services, we may collect some of your information you share with other users. For example:

**Your Payments.** We provide you a number of different payment sources to make transactions securely on our site. For each of these payment sources, we require that third-party sites respect your privacy. During a transaction, we share information related thereto to complete the transaction.

**Adding friends.** When you invite your friends to join Yuuby, we send to them a message with your name, photo, network and other photos in your album profile to notify that you are now on Yuuby. This message may also include other friend suggestions. To check any request pending please to go the [Notifications Page](http://www.yuuby.com/messages/?type=notif). You may remove a friend from your friend list.

**Applications.** Yuuby Apps are in a beta version, their contents will improve soon. For now, you can create apps (such as poll, personality test...). For example, you can create a poll to hear from your friends on a question. Under no circumstances we disclose personal information.

**How friends can find you on Yuuby.** When your friends try to link them to your profile, they send you a friend request. This request may be sent to you if your email address is included in a contact list or by searching through our search engine. You may be found by name or email address. You can restrict your visibility on Yuuby using our [Privacy Settings](http://www.yuuby.com/privacy).

**You and Advertisers.** You may provide your information to advertisers through their advertising contents. If you apply to this, the relationship you create concerns only you and the advertiser. Yuuby guarantees that only the information that you want to pass will reach the advertiser. No other personal information is disclosed.

**Promoting our Services.** We can launch campaigns to promote our services outside our site. When this happens we don't share any information about you.

**Services.** To ensure our services, we may call upon service providers to host our site, providing links, search results, or manage payments. In this case, we have contract provisions to ensure compliance with the privacy of our users. We don't allow these sites to use your data.

**Transfer in the Event of Sale or Change of Control.** If the ownership of all or substantially all of our business changes, we may transfer your information to the new owner so that the service can continue to operate. In such a case, your information would remain subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy.

**Amendments.** We may provide information when a response is required by local laws or if we believe that this information can prevent fraud, moral or physical harm, or if a user violates the [Terms of Use and Responsibilities](http://www.yuuby.com/terms).

Managing Your Information

You may change or delete your information at any time. Here is how we give you ways to manage your information:

**Manage Your Information.** You may edit or delete your profile information from [Edit Profile](http://www.yuuby.com/edit_profile) page. You may also delete comments you posted outside your profile, but you cannot delete a message from your Inbox.

**Deactivating your account.** You can disable your account. In such case, your profile may no longer be accessed by users Yuuby. Up to reactivate your profile, you completely disappear from Yuuby. You will still have the ability to reactivate your account and restore your profile in its entirety. You may deactivate your account on your [Account Settings](http://www.yuuby.com/privacy).

**Deleting your account.** When you delete your Yuuby account, you decide to delete all contents you publish (posts, photos, connections, etc.). You understand that any information you published outside cannot be removed as they are related to other users. You may delete your account from your [Account Settings](http://www.yuuby.com/privacy).

**Backups.** Removed and deleted information may persist in backup copies for up to 90 days, but will not be available to others.

Others

**Limitation of Liability.** We are not responsible for non-respect of your [Account Settings](http://www.yuuby.com/privacy) if you authorize to share information with a third part.

**Amendments.** We may change this Privacy Policy pursuant to the procedures outlined in the Terms of Use. Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. If we make changes to this Privacy Policy we will notify you by publication here and on our {yuuby} Page.

**Definitions.** "Yuuby," "we," "our," "our", "Services" and "Content" mean the same as they do in our [Terms of Use and Responsibilities](http://www.yuuby.com/terms).“Information” and “content” are used more generally and interchangeably here than in the Terms of Use.
